(The late Baek Mi So)
(الراحلة بايك مي سو)
Baek Mi So.
بايك مي سو.
Why is this girl here?
لماذا هذه الفتاة هنا؟
She was only 20 years old, but why...
كانت تبلغ من العمر 20 عامًا فقط، ولكن لماذا...
You don't remember, do you?
أنت لا تتذكر، أليس كذلك؟
At the tender age of 16,
في سن السادسة عشرة،
Mi So jumped from the rooftop of Mingang Distribution...
قفزت مي سو من سطح مبنى شركة مينغانغ للتوزيع...
four years ago.
قبل أربع سنوات.
Do you remember now?
هل تتذكر الآن؟
Who our Mi So is.
من هي مي سو خاصتنا؟
That's ridiculous.
هذا أمر سخيف.
You're insane.
أنت مجنون.
You've completely lost your mind.
لقد فقدت عقلك تماماً.
How could she possibly be my daughter?
كيف يمكن أن تكون ابنتي؟
Say something that makes sense!
قل شيئاً منطقياً!
Then you're saying...
إذن أنت تقول...
with my own hands...
بيدي...
I harmed my own child?
هل آذيت طفلي؟
Don't you dare mess with me.
إياك أن تعبث معي.
If you pull a pathetic stunt like this again,
إذا كررت هذا التصرف البائس،
I'll kill you with my own two hands.
سأقتلك بيديّ الاثنتين.
Did you see that?
هل رأيت ذلك؟
(The late Baek Mi So)
(الراحلة بايك مي سو)
That's the mother who gave birth to you.
هذه هي الأم التي أنجبتك.
She isn't acting like this because she hates you.
إنها لا تتصرف هكذا لأنها تكرهك.
She's just in shock.
إنها في حالة صدمة.
What kind of mother in the world...
أي نوع من الأمهات في العالم...
would disown her own daughter?
هل ستتبرأ من ابنتها؟
Mi So.
الأربعاء الأحد
(The late Baek Mi So)
(الراحلة بايك مي سو)
You can wait a little longer, can't you?
يمكنك الانتظار لفترة أطول قليلاً، أليس كذلك؟
You were always such a good girl.
لطالما كنتِ فتاةً طيبة.
So you can do that, right?
إذن يمكنك فعل ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
(Episode 120)
(الحلقة 120)
How could I be her mother?
كيف لي أن أكون أمها؟
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
What kind of mother would let her own child commit suicide?
أي نوع من الأمهات يسمح لطفله بالانتحار؟
Lucia. You're pulling out all the stops now, aren't you?
لوسيا. أنتِ تبذلين قصارى جهدكِ الآن، أليس كذلك؟
You think I'll even bat an eye?
أتظن أنني سأهتم حتى؟
Whatever tricks you pull,
مهما كانت الحيل التي تستخدمها،
it won't faze me.
لن يزعجني ذلك.
You can't shake me.
لن تستطيع هزيمتي.
I'll never fall for it!
لن أنخدع بذلك أبداً!
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
All I need is my Se Ri.
كل ما أحتاجه هو سي ري.
Only my Se Ri.
فقط سي ري خاصتي.
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
Wait, what happened to the CEO's office?
لحظة، ماذا حدث لمكتب الرئيس التنفيذي؟
Do you have any idea where I've just been?
هل لديك أي فكرة أين كنت للتو؟
The columbarium.
الكولومباريوم.
The columbarium where that girl, Baek Mi So, is laid to rest.
المدفن الذي دُفنت فيه تلك الفتاة، بايك مي سو.
How did you find out about that place?
كيف عرفت عن ذلك المكان؟
You said it yourself last time, didn't you?
قلت ذلك بنفسك في المرة الماضية، أليس كذلك؟
You told me to let you know when I was ready to open Pandora's box.
أخبرتني أن أخبرك عندما أكون مستعداً لفتح صندوق باندورا.
So this is what you were talking about?
إذن هذا ما كنت تتحدث عنه؟
How long have you known?
منذ متى وأنت تعلم؟
You knew all about it and said nothing this entire time?
كنت تعلم بكل شيء ولم تقل شيئاً طوال هذا الوقت؟
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
Answer me!
يجيبني!
Answer me now!
أجبني الآن!
I said, tell me how long you've known, you brat!
قلتُ: أخبرني منذ متى وأنت تعرف، أيها الوغد!
You're in on this with her, aren't you?
أنت متواطئ معها في هذا الأمر، أليس كذلك؟
The two of you cooked this up together, didn't you?
لقد قمتما بتحضير هذا معًا، أليس كذلك؟
What in the world did she promise you?
ما الذي وعدتك به يا ترى؟
What did you get for keeping quiet and making a fool of me all this time?
ماذا جنيت من صمتك وجعلي أضحوكة طوال هذا الوقت؟
Who the heck do you people think you are, toying with me?
من تظنون أنفسكم، تتلاعبون بي؟
Who do you think you are?
من تظن نفسك؟
None of this changes the facts.
لا شيء من هذا يغير الحقائق.
The children were switched 20 years ago,
تم تبديل الأطفال قبل 20 عاماً،
and your daughter is dead.
وابنتك قد ماتت.
Watch your mouth!
احذر من كلامك!
Dead?
ميت؟
Why would my daughter be dead?
لماذا ماتت ابنتي؟
My Se Ri is in the hospital now, but she's going to wake up soon.
سي ري خاصتي في المستشفى الآن، لكنها ستستيقظ قريباً.
She'll walk out of there perfectly healthy.
ستخرج من هناك بصحة جيدة تماماً.
That woman's daughter died, not mine.
ماتت ابنة تلك المرأة، وليس ابنتي.
So what are you going to do now?
إذن، ماذا ستفعل الآن؟
It looks like Baek Sul Hee told CEO Min everything about Baek Mi So.
يبدو أن بايك سول هي أخبرت الرئيس التنفيذي مين بكل شيء عن بايك مي سو.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
What a cruel woman.
يا لها من امرأة قاسية.
She summoned CEO Min to her child's columbarium.
استدعت الرئيس التنفيذي مين إلى مدفن جثث طفلها.
CEO Min didn't even know her child was dead,
لم تكن الرئيسة التنفيذية مين تعلم حتى بوفاة طفلها.
but Sul Hee told her that her child's death was no one else's fault...
لكن سول هي أخبرتها أن وفاة طفلها لم تكن خطأ أي شخص آخر...
but her own.
لكنها هي الخاصة.
That's because it's true.
ذلك لأنه صحيح.
You're the ones who caused all this heartbreak.
أنتم من تسببتم بكل هذا الحزن.
Four years ago,
قبل أربع سنوات،
when that unfortunate incident happened between the two children,
عندما وقع ذلك الحادث المؤسف بين الطفلين،
if you'd just been honest and admitted it, and apologized back then,
لو كنت صادقاً واعترفت بذلك، واعتذرت حينها،
this all would have been over.
كان كل هذا سينتهي.
Who was it that covered it up with lies to the very end?
من الذي قام بالتستر على الأمر بالأكاذيب حتى النهاية؟
We had far too much to lose to apologize.
كان لدينا الكثير لنخسره لدرجة أننا لم نضطر للاعتذار.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I said we're in a different league. Do you think it's easy?
قلتُ إننا في مستوى مختلف. هل تعتقد أن الأمر سهل؟
For the elite to apologize to the lower class.
أن يعتذر النخبة للطبقة الدنيا.
Hey, Kim Sun Jae. You really never change.
يا كيم سون جاي، أنت حقاً لا تتغير أبداً.
This is why they say a leopard can't change its spots.
ولهذا السبب يقولون إن النمر لا يستطيع تغيير جلده.
Who do you think you are to say that to me?
من تظن نفسك حتى تقول لي هذا الكلام؟
It's not just Baek Sul Hee bothering me. You are too, Moon Tae Kyung.
الأمر لا يقتصر على بايك سول هي فقط، بل أنت أيضاً تزعجني يا مون تاي كيونغ.
That's why I propose we end this bad karma right now.
لهذا السبب أقترح أن ننهي هذه الكارما السيئة الآن.
Give Min Doo Sik's slush fund books to the prosecution and turn yourself in.
سلّم دفاتر الأموال السرية الخاصة بـ مين دو سيك إلى النيابة العامة وسلّم نفسك.
And I've already given you my answer to that.
وقد قدمت لك إجابتي على ذلك بالفعل.
That I'll see this through my way.
سأنجز هذا الأمر بطريقتي الخاصة.
As you're set on bringing Min Doo Sik to justice,
بما أنك مصمم على تقديم مين دو سيك للعدالة،
if the aftermath threatens to completely upend my life,
إذا كانت العواقب تهدد بقلب حياتي رأساً على عقب،
I'll fight you and Baek Sul Hee all the way.
سأقاتلك أنت وبايك سول هي حتى النهاية.
Manager Gong, what's going to happen to our family now?
يا مدير غونغ، ماذا سيحدث لعائلتنا الآن؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Think about it. That woman took Father's stake and ran, right?
فكر في الأمر. تلك المرأة أخذت وتد أبي وهربت، أليس كذلك؟
It got out that Kyung Chae is Se Ri's birth mother, right?
اتضح أن كيونغ تشاي هي والدة سي ري البيولوجية، أليس كذلك؟
Se Ri was rescued from the kidnapping, but she's still unconscious.
تم إنقاذ سي ري من عملية الاختطاف، لكنها لا تزال فاقدة للوعي.
Father is in a wheelchair after his stroke.
أصبح الأب على كرسي متحرك بعد إصابته بجلطة دماغية.
How can so much misfortune...
كيف يمكن لكل هذا المصائب أن...
hit our family all at once, like a tsunami?
أصابت عائلتنا جميعاً دفعة واحدة، مثل تسونامي؟
Tell me about it.
أخبرني عن ذلك.
I couldn't sleep a wink last night.
لم أستطع النوم لحظة واحدة الليلة الماضية.
I was worried she'd use Father's stake to officially take the chairman's seat...
كنت قلقاً من أنها ستستخدم حصة والدي لتتولى رسمياً منصب الرئيس...
and kick our whole family out.
ويطردون عائلتنا بأكملها.
Surely she wouldn't do that. Not with Se Ri here.
بالتأكيد لن تفعل ذلك. ليس مع وجود سي ري هنا.
For Se Ri's sake, she can't possibly do something like that.
من أجل سي ري، لا يمكنها أن تفعل شيئاً كهذا.
I'm curious about something.
أنا فضولي بشأن شيء ما.
Manager Gong, last time, we were talking...
المدير غونغ، في المرة الماضية كنا نتحدث...
about something similar and you stopped short.
حول شيء مشابه وتوقفت فجأة.
What's the link between Lucia and Se Ri...
ما هي العلاقة بين لوسيا وسي ري...
that you keep connecting the two of them?
هل تستمر في ربط الاثنين ببعضهما؟
Connect them? What are you talking about?
هل تريد توصيلهما؟ ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Is there some secret story that I don't know about?
هل هناك قصة سرية لا أعرفها؟
A story? Of course not. Stop with the pointless speculation.
قصة؟ بالطبع لا. كفى تكهنات لا طائل منها.
Good grief...
يا إلهي...
Unbelievable.
لا يصدق.
Kyung Chae, what brings you here at this hour?
كيونغ تشاي، ما الذي أتى بكِ إلى هنا في هذا الوقت؟
Where's Manager Gong?
أين المدير غونغ؟
Ms. Kyung Chae.
السيدة كيونغ تشاي.
What...
ماذا...
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Answer my questions and tell me nothing but the truth.
أجب عن أسئلتي ولا تقل لي إلا الحقيقة.
If you lie about a single thing, I'll never see you again.
إذا كذبت بشأن أي شيء، فلن أراك مرة أخرى.
What's going on? You're scaring me.
ما الذي يحدث؟ أنت تُخيفني.
You said...
أنت قلت...
my daughter had stopped breathing...
توقفت ابنتي عن التنفس...
before she arrived at Eulju Hospital 20 years ago, didn't you?
قبل وصولها إلى مستشفى إيولجو قبل 20 عامًا، أليس كذلك؟
In the ambulance,
في سيارة الإسعاف،
in your arms,
بين ذراعيك،
- that was the end, right? - Yes, of course.
- كانت تلك هي النهاية، أليس كذلك؟ - نعم، بالطبع.
- Why do you keep bringing it up? - But...
- لماذا تستمر في إثارة هذا الموضوع؟ - لكن...
Apparently, she didn't die then.
على ما يبدو، لم تمت حينها.
- I heard she was still alive. - What?
- سمعت أنها ما زالت على قيد الحياة. - ماذا؟
That's ridiculous! Who told you that?
هذا سخيف! من أخبرك بهذا؟
Whoever told you that, tell them to stop spouting nonsense.
من أخبرك بذلك، قل له أن يكف عن التفوّه بالهراء.
Your daughter definitely stopped breathing back then.
بالتأكيد توقفت ابنتك عن التنفس في ذلك الوقت.
If that weren't true,
لو لم يكن ذلك صحيحاً،
- why would I have switched the babies? - That's what I said too.
- لماذا كنت سأبدل الأطفال؟ - هذا ما قلته أنا أيضاً.
That it was all nonsense.
كان كل ذلك هراءً.
Then why are you still so worked up?
إذاً لماذا ما زلت متوتراً للغاية؟
It's just some ridiculous rumor. You should just ignore it.
إنها مجرد إشاعة سخيفة. عليك تجاهلها.
I can't ignore it.
لا يمكنني تجاهل ذلك.
What?
ماذا؟
I said I can't ignore it.
قلتُ إنني لا أستطيع تجاهل الأمر.
I have to find out for myself.
يجب أن أكتشف ذلك بنفسي.
I'm trying to find a mother and child from 20 years ago.
أحاول العثور على صورة لأم وطفلها من عشرين عاماً مضت.
They were brought in by ambulance after she gave birth.
تم نقلهم بواسطة سيارة إسعاف بعد ولادتها.
And you don't know the exact date?
وأنت لا تعرف التاريخ المحدد؟
September 28, 2006.
28 سبتمبر 2006.
A new mother and her baby. They came here via the Anpyeong highway.
أم جديدة وطفلها. وصلوا إلى هنا عبر طريق أنبيونغ السريع.
Actually, never mind the mother.
في الحقيقة، لا داعي للقلق بشأن الأم.
I just need to know what happened to the baby.
أريد فقط أن أعرف ماذا حدث للطفل.
I was told she died for certain.
قيل لي إنها ماتت بالتأكيد.
I need you to check her condition upon arrival,
أحتاج منك أن تفحص حالتها عند وصولها.
whether she was actually dead...
سواء كانت ميتة بالفعل...
or if she was barely clinging to life.
أو إذا كانت بالكاد تتمسك بالحياة.
That's confidential personal information, so we aren't at liberty to disclose.
هذه معلومات شخصية سرية، لذا لا يحق لنا الكشف عنها.
Someone's life is at stake! Who cares about a privacy policy?
حياة أحدهم في خطر! من يهتم بسياسة الخصوصية؟
What if you thought your child was dead?
ماذا لو ظننت أن طفلك قد مات؟
What if the child whose mother thought she was dead was actually alive,
ماذا لو كان الطفل الذي ظنت أمه أنها ماتت على قيد الحياة بالفعل؟
and without knowing anything,
وبدون أن يعلم أي شيء،
the mother ended up causing that child’s death?
هل تسببت الأم في وفاة ذلك الطفل؟
Ma'am, I'm not sure I understand what you're saying.
سيدتي، لست متأكدًا من أنني أفهم ما تقولينه.
I said find out now if my daughter lived or died!
قلتُ: اكتشفوا الآن ما إذا كانت ابنتي قد عاشت أم ماتت!
Find out if that woman saved my daughter! Find out right now!
اكتشفوا ما إذا كانت تلك المرأة قد أنقذت ابنتي! اكتشفوا ذلك الآن!
Ma'am, please calm down.
سيدتي، من فضلكِ اهدئي.
Father hasn't touched his food again?
ألم يلمس أبي طعامه مرة أخرى؟
- No, he hasn't. - Gosh, how many days has it been?
- لا، لم يفعل. - يا إلهي، كم يوماً مرّ؟
At this rate, we'll be planning his funeral.
وبهذا المعدل، سنكون بصدد التخطيط لجنازته.
Considering everything that's going on in this family,
بالنظر إلى كل ما يحدث في هذه العائلة،
I can't say I blame him for not having an appetite.
لا أستطيع أن ألومه على عدم وجود شهية لديه.
To put it lightly, it's a complete mess.
وبكل بساطة، إنها فوضى عارمة.
Anyway, shouldn't we go visit Se Ri?
على أي حال، ألا يجب أن نذهب لزيارة سي ري؟
I'm her brother. I should at least visit her in the hospital.
أنا أخوها. يجب عليّ على الأقل زيارتها في المستشفى.
You're not her brother, you're her uncle now.
أنت لست شقيقها، أنت عمها الآن.
Is that our relation now?
هل هذه هي علاقتنا الآن؟
Whatever our relation is, she's still lying in that hospital bed.
مهما كانت علاقتنا، فهي لا تزال طريحة الفراش في ذلك المستشفى.
She's in the ICU, so it's not like you can visit anyway.
إنها في وحدة العناية المركزة، لذا لا يمكنك زيارتها على أي حال.
Besides, I'm sure Kyung Chae is taking good care of her.
إلى جانب ذلك، أنا متأكدة من أن كيونغ تشاي تعتني بها جيداً.
Se Ri is her own flesh and blood.
سي ري هي من لحمها ودمها.
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
It's so unfair!
هذا ظلم كبير!
It's so unfair I could die, Mother!
هذا ظلم كبير لدرجة أنني قد أموت يا أمي!
Why did you do this to me?
لماذا فعلت بي هذا؟
Why did you let me die feeling so wronged?
لماذا تركتني أموت وأنا أشعر بهذا الظلم؟
Why on earth would you do that? Why?
لماذا قد تفعل ذلك؟ لماذا؟
You're the one who gave birth to me!
أنتِ من أنجبتني!
What mother would do that to her daughter?
أي أم ستفعل ذلك بابنتها؟
What kind of mother lets her daughter die?
أي نوع من الأمهات يسمح لابنته بالموت؟
Why are you taking Mi So's things?
لماذا تأخذ أغراض مي سو؟
You should just leave them here. So you can see them when you miss her.
يجب أن تتركها هنا. حتى تتمكن من رؤيتها عندما تشتاق إليها.
I think there's someone who's more curious to see them than I am.
أعتقد أن هناك من هو أكثر فضولاً لرؤيتهم مني.
Who?
من؟
Min Kyung Chae?
مين كيونغ تشاي؟
But isn't she denying that Mi So is even her daughter?
لكن ألا تنكر أنها ابنتها أصلاً؟
Anyone in her position would find it hard to accept.
أي شخص في وضعها سيجد صعوبة في تقبل ذلك.
Well, she should have lived her life right.
كان ينبغي عليها أن تعيش حياتها بشكل صحيح.
Relying on the power of Mingang Distribution,
بالاعتماد على قوة شركة مينغانغ للتوزيع،
sitting in her cushy job with the world at her feet...
تجلس في وظيفتها المريحة والعالم بين يديها...
she was unbearably arrogant, wasn't she?
كانت متغطرسة بشكل لا يطاق، أليس كذلك؟
Everyone else must have looked like a joke to her.
لا بد أن كل شخص آخر بدا لها وكأنه مزحة.
That's why...
لهذا السبب...
even after driving a 16-year-old to suicide from the sheer injustice,
حتى بعد أن تسبب الظلم الفادح في انتحار فتاة تبلغ من العمر 16 عامًا ،
she doesn't feel an ounce of shame or remorse.
إنها لا تشعر بذرة من الخجل أو الندم.
Be careful.
احرص.
Oh my gosh. Where on earth did you get so hurt?
يا إلهي! أين تعرضتَ لهذه الإصابة الخطيرة؟
Manager Gong.
المدير غونغ.
Se Ri is my daughter, isn't she?
سي ري هي ابنتي، أليس كذلك؟
Of course. What a thing to say.
بالتأكيد. يا له من كلام!
Why? Did someone say she's not?
لماذا؟ هل قال أحدهم إنها ليست كذلك؟
Who said that?
من قال ذلك؟
You two are the very picture of a mother and daughter.
أنتما مثالٌ حيٌّ للأم وابنتها.
So, a mother...
إذن، الأم...
is supposed to protect her own child, right?
من المفترض أن تحمي طفلها، أليس كذلك؟
No matter what happens,
بغض النظر عما يحدث،
a mother's job is to protect her child, isn't it?
أليس من واجب الأم حماية طفلها؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Parents exist to protect their children.
يوجد الآباء لحماية أطفالهم.
If anyone tries to take your child away, you have to stop them.
إذا حاول أي شخص أخذ طفلك، فعليك منعه.
You have to stop them even if it costs you your life.
عليك إيقافهم حتى لو كلفك ذلك حياتك.
Risk my life to stop them?
هل أُخاطر بحياتي لإيقافهم؟
(Mingang Distribution)
(توزيع)
These were Mi So's.
كانت هذه هي مي سو.
I thought you'd be curious.
ظننت أنك ستكون فضولياً.
We were struggling so much we couldn't afford a first birthday party,
كنا نعاني من ضائقة مالية شديدة لدرجة أننا لم نتمكن من تحمل تكاليف حفلة عيد الميلاد الأول.
and we couldn't afford preschool, so there are no photos from school plays.
ولم نكن نستطيع تحمل تكاليف مرحلة ما قبل المدرسة، لذلك لا توجد صور من المسرحيات المدرسية.
But she was a good student and won quite a few academic awards.
لكنها كانت طالبة جيدة وحصلت على عدد لا بأس به من الجوائز الأكاديمية.
They're all in here.
جميعهم هنا.
(CEO Min Kyung Chae)
(الرئيس التنفيذي مين كيونغ تشاي)
This is...
هذا هو...
her early acceptance letter to the international high school.
رسالة قبولها المبكر في المدرسة الثانوية الدولية.
And this...
وهذا...
is the uniform we had made for her, but she never got to wear it.
هذا هو الزي الذي صنعناه لها، لكنها لم ترتديه قط.
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
هل أنت مجنون؟ ماذا تفعل؟
What do you think you're doing?
ما الذي تظن نفسك فاعلاً؟
What kind of sick stunt is this?
ما هذا النوع من الحركات المريضة؟
Why should I have to look at your dead daughter's things?
لماذا يجب عليّ أن أنظر إلى أغراض ابنتك المتوفاة؟
Why are you making a scene over this junk?
لماذا تُثير كل هذه الضجة بسبب هذه الخردة؟
If they're so precious, you can stare at them all you want.
إذا كانت هذه الأشياء ثمينة للغاية، فيمكنك التحديق فيها كما تشاء.
They're nothing but trash to me.
إنهم لا يمثلون لي سوى قمامة.
"Trash?"
"نفاية؟"
How can you call your own child's mementos trash?
كيف يمكنك أن تصف تذكارات طفلك بالقمامة؟
What child?
أي طفل؟
Who on earth are you calling my child?
من تقصد بـ"طفلي"؟
My daughter is Se Ri.
ابنتي اسمها سي ري.
No matter how much you insist, that fact won't change.
مهما أصررتَ، لن تتغير هذه الحقيقة.
You must have lost your mind after your daughter's death.
لا بد أنك فقدت عقلك بعد وفاة ابنتك.
Look.
ينظر.
Snap out of it.
استفق من غفلتك.
Do you think that's going to bring her back to life?
هل تعتقد أن ذلك سيعيدها إلى الحياة؟
If you're going to lose your mind, at least have some class.
إذا كنت ستفقد عقلك، فعلى الأقل تحلى ببعض الرقي.
You can't just go around claiming someone else's daughter is yours.
لا يمكنك ببساطة أن تدّعي أن ابنة شخص آخر هي ابنتك.
You think that'll make her your daughter?
أتظن أن ذلك سيجعلها ابنتك؟
Just because your own daughter is dead,
لمجرد أن ابنتك قد ماتت،
you're just trying to take Se Ri from me.
أنت تحاول فقط أن تأخذ سي ري مني.
So just stop it.
لذا توقف عن ذلك.
Keep this up, and I won't be so nice.
استمروا على هذا المنوال، ولن أكون لطيفاً معكم.
Who's Mi So?
من هي مي سو؟
Who is she?
من هي؟
I don't know her.
أنا لا أعرفها.
I don't need some kid like that.
لا أحتاج إلى طفل كهذا.
All I need is my Se Ri.
كل ما أحتاجه هو سي ري.
Once my Se Ri wakes up,
بمجرد أن تستيقظ منطقة سي ري لدي،
everything will be fine. There won't be any problem at all.
كل شيء سيكون على ما يرام. لن تكون هناك أي مشكلة على الإطلاق.
No matter what anyone says.
بغض النظر عما يقوله أي شخص.
Se Ri is my daughter. What can she do about it?
سي ري ابنتي. ماذا يمكنها أن تفعل حيال ذلك؟
Some stupid DNA test?
اختبار الحمض النووي الغبي؟
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
Like that's such a big deal.
وكأن هذا أمرٌ جلل.
The whole world knows that Se Ri is my daughter.
العالم كله يعلم أن سي ري هي ابنتي.
Who does she think she is?
من تظن نفسها؟
What are you doing out here?
ماذا تفعل هنا؟
Perfect timing, Lawyer Kim.
توقيت مثالي يا محامية كيم.
I think Lucia is completely lost her mind.
أعتقد أن لوسيا قد فقدت عقلها تماماً.
Excuse me?
اعذرني؟
Can you believe it? She tried to give me mementos from some girl named Mi So.
هل تصدق ذلك؟ لقد حاولت أن تعطيني تذكارات من فتاة تدعى مي سو.
Why on earth would I take the things of someone else's dead child...
لماذا قد آخذ أغراض طفل متوفى لشخص آخر؟
when my own daughter is clearly still alive?
في حين أن ابنتي لا تزال على قيد الحياة؟
We need to act fast.
علينا أن نتحرك بسرعة.
If we don't get her out of the company, there will be hell to pay.
إذا لم نخرجها من الشركة، فسيكون هناك ثمن باهظ سندفعه.
She's already lost it and can't tell her child from a stranger's.
لقد فقدت صوابها بالفعل، ولم تعد قادرة على التمييز بين طفلها وطفل غريب.
We can't just let that slide, can we?
لا يمكننا أن نتجاهل ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
That's why you have to help me.
لهذا السبب عليك مساعدتي.
We have to force that woman out.
علينا إجبار تلك المرأة على الرحيل.
To protect the company and Se Ri.
لحماية الشركة وشركة سي ري.
Okay?
تمام؟
What the heck did you do?
ماذا فعلت بحق الجحيم؟
What did you do to make CEO Min react like that?
ما الذي فعلته لتجعل الرئيس التنفيذي مين يتصرف بهذه الطريقة؟
I gave her Mi So's things.
أعطيتها أغراض مي سو.
She's the birth mother. She deserves to know.
هي الأم البيولوجية. من حقها أن تعرف.
Are you out of your mind?
هل فقدت عقلك؟
Would you want to face a child who died because of you?
هل ترغب في مواجهة طفل مات بسببك؟
I'm not trying to make her feel good.
أنا لا أحاول أن أجعلها تشعر بالرضا.
I'm not trying to torment Min Kyung Chae, either.
أنا أيضاً لا أحاول مضايقة مين كيونغ تشاي.
I did that hoping she would accept the truth,
فعلت ذلك على أمل أن تتقبل الحقيقة.
atone for her past, and beg for forgiveness.
تكفّر عن ماضيها، وتتوسل المغفرة.
Because the wrongs of the past must be made right.
لأن أخطاء الماضي يجب تصحيحها.
My Mi So...
ماي مي سو...
She was an innocent victim in that assault case four years ago.
لقد كانت ضحية بريئة في قضية الاعتداء تلك قبل أربع سنوات.
But you people twisted the truth with your money, power, and connections!
لكنكم حرّفتم الحقيقة بأموالكم وسلطتكم وعلاقاتكم!
I'm here to set things right again.
أنا هنا لأصلح الأمور من جديد.
And to do that, she has to face reality first.
ولكي تفعل ذلك، عليها أن تواجه الواقع أولاً.
Can you just get the heck out of here, will you?
هل يمكنك أن تخرج من هنا فوراً ؟
The past is in the past. Why are you dredging it all up now?
الماضي قد مضى. لماذا تنبش كل ذلك الآن؟
No!
لا!
I'm going to make this right, starting now.
سأصلح هذا الوضع، بدءاً من الآن.
All the filthy lies you smeared my Mi So's name with!
كل الأكاذيب القذرة التي لطخت بها اسم مي سو خاصتي!
Feeding her to the media for a witch hunt!
تقديمها لوسائل الإعلام في حملة مطاردة الساحرات!
I'm going to clear her name.
سأبرئ ساحتها.
- Do we really have to go this far? - The shaman said it himself.
- هل يجب علينا حقاً أن نذهب إلى هذا الحد؟ - قالها الشامان بنفسه.
Our house is east, which is bad,
منزلنا يقع في الشرق، وهذا أمر سيء.
and Chairman Min's is in the west, so that's out too.
ومطعم الرئيس مين يقع في الغرب، لذا فهو مستبعد أيضاً.
He said a spot in the south, by the water, is the perfect place.
وقال إن بقعة في الجنوب، بجوار الماء، هي المكان المثالي.
This is a Korean spa. It's full of heat, not water.
هذا منتجع صحي كوري. إنه مليء بالحرارة، وليس بالماء.
No, they have baths with plenty of water. It has water, too.
لا، لديهم حمامات بها الكثير من الماء. يوجد بها ماء أيضاً.
Wait a minute. You know, the more I think on it, the angrier I get.
لحظة من فضلك. كلما فكرت في الأمر أكثر، كلما ازداد غضبي.
How can one talisman cost a whole grand?
كيف يمكن أن يكلف تميمة واحدة ألف دولار؟
They say the more expensive it is, the more potent it is.
يقولون إن كلما زاد سعره، زادت فعاليته.
How can you be so cheap about something like this?
كيف يمكنك أن تكون بخيلاً إلى هذا الحد في أمر كهذا؟
All the good energy from that money is getting stored up in this.
كل الطاقة الإيجابية الناتجة عن تلك الأموال تتراكم في هذا المكان.
Money is the best thing in the world. Nothing shows devotion like hard cash.
المال هو أفضل شيء في العالم. لا شيء يُظهر الإخلاص مثل المال النقدي.
- Money, money, money! - Money, money, money, money, money!
- المال، المال، المال! - المال، المال، المال، المال، المال!
- Mom. Dad.
- أمي. أبي.
- You're here. - You made it.
- أنت هنا. - لقد نجحت.
Why did you make me come all this way? You think this will change anything?
لماذا جعلتني أقطع كل هذه المسافة؟ أتظن أن هذا سيغير أي شيء؟
Hey! Take it back now! Seriously!
مهلاً! تراجع عن كلامك الآن! بجدية!
You shouldn't say things that could jinx us.
لا ينبغي أن تقول أشياء قد تجلب لنا النحس.
Ptooey, like this?
تباً، هكذا؟
Yes, good girl. Now, make sure to keep this with you at all times.
أحسنتِ يا فتاة. الآن، تأكدي من الاحتفاظ بهذا معكِ في جميع الأوقات.
Don't ever take it off. And put one in Ji Seop's underwear.
لا تنزعه أبداً. وضع واحداً في ملابس جي سوب الداخلية.
That cost a pretty penny, you know.
لقد كلف ذلك مبلغاً كبيراً، كما تعلم.
Money, money, money.
المال، المال، المال.
Money is intention, and intention is money.
المال هو النية، والنية هي المال.
All right. I'll keep it with me.
حسناً. سأحتفظ به معي.
But is this supposed to get rid of bad luck?
لكن هل من المفترض أن يزيل هذا سوء الحظ؟
Hey, there you go again. I told you not to say things that jinx it!
ها أنت ذا تفعلها مجدداً. لقد حذرتك من قول أشياء تجلب النحس!
She's right. Ji Seop's family isn't functional right now, is it?
هي محقة. عائلة جي سوب ليست متماسكة في الوقت الحالي، أليس كذلك؟
It's one disaster after another there. You must do this to avoid bad luck.
إنها كارثة تلو الأخرى هناك. عليك فعل هذا لتجنب سوء الحظ.
Anyway, let's just head inside. Come on.
على أي حال، فلندخل إلى الداخل. هيا بنا.
Let's go in.
هيا ندخل.
(Women's Bath Entrance)
(مدخل حمام النساء)
Oh my, are you crazy?
يا إلهي، هل أنت مجنون؟
- Are you crazy? Where are you going? - You're insane!
- هل أنت مجنون؟ إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟ - أنت مجنون!
This is the women's bathhouse!
هذا حمام النساء!
- Oh my! - He's really lost it!
يا إلهي! لقد فقد صوابه تماماً!
Honestly, he's ridiculous.
بصراحة، إنه مثير للسخرية.
You're coming with me.
ستأتي معي.
And where are you trying to drag me now?
وإلى أين تحاول جرّي الآن؟
We're going to every TV station and newspaper office.
سنزور جميع محطات التلفزيون ومكاتب الصحف.
We should visit all those places that twisted the stories...
ينبغي علينا زيارة جميع تلك الأماكن التي حرّفت القصص...
of my Mi So's assault and published trash stories four years ago.
عن اعتداء صديقتي مي سو ونشرها قصصاً تافهة قبل أربع سنوات.
We're going to set the record straight!
سنقوم بتصحيح الأمور!
And why would I go there with you?
ولماذا سأذهب إلى هناك معك؟
Because she's your daughter. Will you pretend this doesn't concern you?
لأنها ابنتك. هل ستتظاهر بأن هذا الأمر لا يعنيك؟
- What kind of mother would do that? - Who are you calling my daughter?
- أي نوع من الأمهات يفعل ذلك؟ - من تقصدين بابنتي؟
I told you, she's not my daughter!
قلت لك، إنها ليست ابنتي!
My daughter's name is Se Ri.
اسم ابنتي سي ري.
Why do you keep forcing your dead daughter on me?
لماذا تستمر في إجباري على رؤية ابنتك المتوفاة؟
Are you that desperate to pawn her off on me?
هل أنت يائسٌ لهذه الدرجة لتتخلص منها وتعطيني إياها؟
Then again,
ثم مرة أخرى،
you couldn't protect her child, so you must feel like a criminal.
لم تستطع حماية طفلها، لذا لا بد أنك تشعر وكأنك مجرم.
But don't you dare push that guilt onto me.
لكن إياك أن تلقي بهذا الذنب عليّ.
By insisting your dead daughter is mine,
بإصرارك على أن ابنتك المتوفاة هي ابنتي،
are you trying to steal my daughter who's still alive?
هل تحاول سرقة ابنتي التي لا تزال على قيد الحياة؟
You think I'd let you?
أتظن أنني سأسمح لك بذلك؟
Lose my daughter to someone like you?
أخسر ابنتي لشخص مثلك؟
I'll never let you take her.
لن أسمح لك بأخذها أبداً.
Because Mi So is your daughter.
لأن مي سو هي ابنتك.
The daughter you destroyed!
الابنة التي دمرتها!
No! She is not my daughter!
لا! إنها ليست ابنتي!
Come with me.
تعال معي.
- Let go! - Come!
- اتركني! - هيا!
What do you think you're doing?
ما الذي تظن نفسك فاعلاً؟
- Let go of me! - I said, come with me!
- اتركني! - قلتُ، تعال معي!
- Where are you taking me? - Come with me.
- إلى أين تأخذني؟ - تعال معي.
Hurry up!
أسرع!
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
Get over here!
تعال إلى هنا!
- Let go of me! - Come on!
- اتركني! - هيا!
Take a good, hard look at what happened to your daughter right here!
ألقِ نظرة فاحصة على ما حدث لابنتك هنا!
What daughter?
أي ابنة؟
I said, take a good look at what you did back then!
قلتُ: ألقِ نظرة جيدة على ما فعلته في ذلك الوقت!
Come here!
تعال الى هنا!
See what our Mi So must have felt when she jumped from this very spot.
انظروا ماذا شعرت مي سو عندما قفزت من هذا المكان بالذات.
Let go of me!
اتركني!
- Let go of me! - Lucia!
- اتركيني! - لوسيا!
You can't force her like this. It won't work.
لا يمكنك إجبارها بهذه الطريقة. لن ينجح الأمر.
If she can't even accept her own daughter, how can she right the wrongs of the past?
إذا كانت لا تستطيع حتى أن تتقبل ابنتها، فكيف لها أن تصلح أخطاء الماضي؟
She doesn't feel the least bit sorry for Mi So.
إنها لا تشعر بأي شفقة تجاه مي سو.
Admitting to Mi So would mean exposing her own shameful past.
إن اعترافها لمي سو يعني كشف ماضيها المخزي.
That's not going to be easy for her.
لن يكون ذلك سهلاً عليها.
Just an "I'm sorry"...
مجرد كلمة "أنا آسف"...
That's all it would take.
هذا كل ما يتطلبه الأمر.
It's not going to happen today.
لن يحدث ذلك اليوم.
Let's just go home for now. You look terribly pale.
لنذهب إلى المنزل الآن. تبدو شاحباً للغاية.
If my Se Ri wakes up...
إذا استيقظت سي ري خاصتي...
and finds out that woman is her birth mother...
وتكتشف أن تلك المرأة هي والدتها البيولوجية...
And what if she leaves me?
وماذا لو تركتني؟
No! Absolutely not!
لا! قطعاً لا!
The second Se Ri wakes up, that woman will spill everything.
بمجرد أن تستيقظ سي ري، ستكشف تلك المرأة كل شيء.
That's why she's always hanging around the hospital...
ولهذا السبب فهي دائماً ما تتسكع حول المستشفى...
and clinging to Se Ri's side.
وتشبث بجانب سي ري.
I need to get rid of that woman.
أحتاج إلى التخلص من تلك المرأة.
I have to protect my daughter.
يجب عليّ حماية ابنتي.
A mother can't let her child be taken away.
لا يمكن للأم أن تسمح بأخذ طفلها منها.
That's not being a mother.
هذا ليس ما يُسمى بالأمومة.
Wait here for a second.
انتظر هنا لحظة.
(The Woman Who Swallowed the Sun)
(المرأة التي ابتلعت الشمس)
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)
(الترجمة مقدمة من KOCOWA.)